naruto-arena.com 2017-12-03

# Privacy policy - Naruto Arena

##### Privacy Policy

The following webpage outlines Naruto-Arena's collection and use of personal information from it's users. Naruto-Arena values the privacy of our members and users, we will never share any personal information of anybody who logs on to Naruto-Arena with anyone. This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon logging on to Naruto-Arena such things as your IP address and hostname are logged for statistical and security reasons. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a user's web browser by a website or ad server. We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services. 

##### What we collect

We may collect the following information:  
\- information your web browser automatically sends to our server like the IP address and page you requested  
\- demographic and geographic information such as a country, age or gender via google analytics  
\- contact information including email address

##### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
\- Internal record keeping.  
\- We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
\- We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
\- From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

##### Can I opt-out for Google Analytics features?

You can opt-out by using [the following url.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

##### Children's Privacy

Naruto-Arena does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of Naruto-Arena, and will not collect information from them. If Naruto-Arena learns that a child under the age of 13 has become a member, we will close that child's account and delete any information collected about the child. 

Not withstanding the foregoing, Naruto-Arena may choose to retain some personal information such as the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child. 

##### Disclosing Information

Naruto-Arena may store and disclose personal information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety, and property of Naruto-Arena, users of the Naruto-Arena website, and the public. 

##### Security

a At Naruto-Arena we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on Naruto-Arena and it's affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated. 

##### Third Parties

Third Party websites may collect information from users of Naruto-Arena, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. Some programs that may collect this information include: eXTReMe Tracking, Nedstat, and Webalizer. 

Additionally, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

##### Website Policy Changes

Naruto-Arena reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. If you have any comments, questions, or concerns regaurding this policy, or any other policy you may send them to us at policy@naruto-arena.com 

By continuing to access Naruto-Arena and any of it's affiliated websites and files, you are expressly and impliedly agreeing to all of the terms as stated above on this document. You also hereby affirm that you are in compliance with all Federal, State and Local laws in your place of residence concerning the contents of Naruto-Arena, and are also in agreeance with our disclaimer and terms of use.
